wallpaperstudio10.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy | Tens of thousands HD and UltraHD wallpapers for Android, Windows and Xbox

Updated: 05-21-2018

**1\. General Statements**  
Wallpaper Studio 10 is a website and application as services (“Services”) created, developed and owned by good2create.  
This document outlines the types of information collected by our Wallpaper Studio 10 “Services”. Wallpaper Studio 10 provides a photo hosting service to you, subject to the following Privacy Policy, which may be updated from time to time without notice to you.  
This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the “Services”, and when you access, download, purchase or use any information, services, products or content appearing in the “Services”.  
By using the “Services”, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in the Privacy Policy.

**2\. User Accounts**  
No user account is required to browse or download the content we provide. User account is only required to use the login required area, the “Registered Area” of the “Services”.  
Registered area:  
There are some parts and functions of the “Services” which required a registration to use.  
These parts and functions are the following:  
Web page: 

  * Uploading wallpapers
  * Commenting to the wallpapers
  * Following publishers
  * Creating personal wallpaper lists such as favorite, folders and history in which the folder can be made publicly available.

Applications: 

  * Uploading wallpapers
  * Commenting to the wallpapers
  * Following publishers
  * Synchronizing personal wallpaper lists through devices like favorite, folders and history in which the folder can be made publicly available.

**3\. User Provided Information**

a. What type of information are we collect and store?  
We are collecting and storing the following information about you when you register to the “Services”. Only the publisher name is mandatory to use the “Registered Area” of the “Services”. 

  * Publisher name
  * Profile photo (Optional)
  * Name (Optional)
  * E-mail (Optional)
  * Gender (Optional)
  * Age (Optional)
  * Country (Optional)
  * Web page (Optional)

The profile photo, gender, age, and country can be set private which means no one else but the user can see this information.

b. What this information are used for?  
In every case, the publisher name and profile photo (if not private) can be seen on the following parts of the “Services”: 

  * Your public profile page
  * Top publishers list
  * Your uploaded wallpaper’s page
  * Your comments
  * Your public collections’ page
  * Followed and following publisher lists
  * Other wallpaper or publisher recommendation panel

Your uploaded wallpaper’s page and your public profile page can optionally contain the following information if provided and not set private: gender, age, country, and web page.  
Your name and e-mail address never can be seen public and only you and the “Services” owner can access this information.  
Your name and e-mail address are used for transactional emails such as: 

  * Welcome e-mail
  * User statistics e-mails (ie: weekly report)

c. How we store this information?  
We store your information in a database (MySQL) on a server located in Frankfurt, Germany. There are three more servers which can access this database directly located in Frankfurt, Germany, New York, United States, and Tokyo, Japan.  
We do our best to secure the servers, database, and database/server connections and communications using the latest technology such as security services, encryptions and others.

d. How you can view, modify or delete the information stored about you?  
Our “Services” has a so-called Account page where you can view, edit or delete all your information.  
You can access the Account Page in the following way:  
Application (Windows and Android):  
Hamburger menu (Navigation Drawer) - > Account  
Web page:  
When you logged in use the Account -> My Account menu in the top right corner.  
You can view, modify, or delete your account information on the Account page using the “Edit Profile Info” button.  
You can find "Delete account" menu in applications in the following way: Account page -> Delete account menu in the top right corner.  
You can also ask for your account deletion sending a request to info@wallpaperstudio10.com email address. We will response your request within 3 working days.  
When you delete your account we immediately remove every personal information from our database and the information will be deleted from all our cache and backup within 10 days.  
Your can deactivate your photos before account deletion. Deactivated photos can not be seen in publicly. Any wallpaper not deactivated before the account deletion will be continuously available but all personal information will be removed.

e. Why we collect this information?  
We collect and store your information because you granted permission for us upon accepting our “Terms and Condition” and “Privacy Policy” in the registration process.  
We ask for this information only to personalize and socialize our “Services”.

f. Who we share your information with?  
We never give access to third party which are not enlisted in the following list: 

  * SendGrid: We use SendGrid service to send our transactional e-mails. The name and e-mail address are provided to this service. More information about SendGrid Privacy Policy: https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy 
  * Push Notification: We never give access to personal information to the services used to send push notification to the “Services” users.  
You can unsubscribe in the following way from the push notification:  
Web: Using the web browser (Chrome, Firefox, Microsoft Edge, etc.) own setting to unsubscribe from push notification.  
Application: You can unsubscribe from Push Notifications in Hamburger menu (Navigation Drawer) -> Settings -> Enable or disable Push Notifications.  
The following services are user for sending push notifications: Microsoft WNS service (https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/), Google GCM service (https://privacy.google.com/), SendPulse web push notification service (https://sendpulse.com/legal/pp)  

  * Anonym information and database about using the “Services” like Google Analytics, Microsoft Store, and Play Store statistics. 

g. How long we store this information?  
We store your information until account deletion. When you delete your account we immediately remove every personal information from our database and the information will be deleted from all our cache and backup within 10 days.

h. How you can download all your personal information stored in our “Services”?  
You can download all your data stored in our “Services” in JSON format with the “Account information Export” button.  
This button can be reached in the following way:  
Web:  
When you logged in use the Account -> Export Account Info menu in the top right corner.  
Applications:  
Account page -> Export Account Info menu in the top right corner.  
Even with all the appropriate precautions we take to protect your information, we recommend you refrain from sending private information or Personal.

**4\. Information from Use of our Services**  
Good2create also gathers non-personally identifiable information from Users of our Services. Non-personally identifiable information is information that usually cannot by itself be used to identify a particular person or entity, and may include: the Internet Protocol (IP) address, unique device identifiers, anonymous IDs for advertising, operating system, mobile network information and non-precise device location information (e.g., city or region).

**5\. User generated Content**  
We offer our Users the opportunity to upload images. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Service. Users agree that the uploaded images will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

**6\. Social authentication provider login**  
When you choose to login to Wallpaper Studio 10 with any of the social authentication providers (Microsoft, Facebook or Google+) we can access certain information you've added on the mentioned social providers to prefill your profile information and identify you. You can modify or delete this prefilled information during the registration process or any time in the “Edit personal information” section. If you modify or delete this information we never store the information fetched from the social providers.  
We request the following information from the social providers:

  * Name
  * E-mail
  * Age
  * Country
  * Gender
  * Profile photo

**7\. Third-Party Advertisers**  
Wallpaper Studio 10 serves ads provided by a range of third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by Wallpaper Studio 10’s privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience we provide a list our advertising partners below.  
Google AdSense (https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)  
Google AdMob (https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads)  
AdDuplex (https://www.adduplex.com/privacy-policy)  
Microsoft Advertising (https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/)

**10\. Children's Privacy**  
We do not direct the “Services” to persons under 13 years of age, and requires Users to be 13 years or older. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect or maintain on the Site personally identifying or other information from persons under 13 years of age. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us through our info@wallpaperstudio10.com email address. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.  
We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask a parent or guardian for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. 

**11\. Cookies**  
When you visit any web site, it may store or retrieve information on your browser, mostly in the form of cookies. This information might be about you, your preferences or your device and is mostly used to make the site work as you expect it to. The information does not usually directly identify you, but it can give you a more personalised web experience. Because we respect your right to privacy, you can choose not to allow some types of cookies. Click on the Change your current Cookie Settings link to find out more and change your settings. However, blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer.

Change your current Cookie Settings

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. Please send us feedback pertaining to these matters or any other issue you may have with Wallpaper Studio 10. General contact: [info@wallpaperstudio10.com](mailto:info@wallpaperstudio10.com)  
Privacy contact: [privacy@wallpaperstudio10.com](mailto:privacy@wallpaperstudio10.com)
